# **Jacob Lammert**

FRONT END DEVELOPER

# **Profile**

I am a front end developer with a passion for creating beautiful and functional websites. I take pride in my reliability and love getting projects done on time. I have a firm grasp of HTML, CSS, Javascript, and WordPress, as well as experience with React and PHP.

# **Employment History**

### Oil Change Technician, Jiffy Lube, Benicia

AUGUST 2017 - MAY 2021

- Perform oil changes and other automotive maintenance services.
- Inspect vehicle to identify potential problems and advise customers on necessary repairs.
- Ensure customer satisfaction and provide customer feedback.
- Maintain a clean and safe work environment.
- Adhere to all company policies and procedures.
- Keep accurate and up-to-date records of services performed.
- Maintain a current knowledge of automotive services and products.

#### Camp Counselor, Camp Bow Wow, Pleasant Hill

MAY 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Responsible for providing customer service to dog owners and dogs in a safe and fun environment.
- Ensuring the safety and well-being of all dogs and visitors at all times.
- Supervising play groups of up to 20 dogs, monitoring their behavior, and intervening when necessary.
- Maintaining a clean and sanitary environment for all dogs and visitors.
- Providing exercise, playtime, and socialization for all dogs.

#### Pet Bather, Bubbly Bulldog Grooming, Benicia

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Provide professional bathing services for dogs in grooming facility
- Perform all aspects of bathing, trimming, and cleaning of dogs
- Created the companies website
- Demonstrate safe handling of dogs of all breeds and sizes
- Provide additional services to customers such as nail trimming, ear cleaning, and teeth brushing

# **Education**

#### Computer Science Associate Degree, Diablo Valley College, Pleasant Hill

MAY 2022

I took courses in programming, web design, and data structures to gain a better understanding of the basics of computer science. I applied the knowledge I gained in these classes to my own projects and began to create websites and applications.

#### **Details**

Benicia United States 7073861975 jacoblammert9@gmail.com

# Links

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub

## **Skills**

HTML5

CSS
JavaScript
Wordpress
React

#### **Hobbies**

Movies, Video Games, Video Editing

#### Languages

**English** 

Spanish